[Music] I do
n't know if we can really make it. Dad, Dad,
Dad. Right, it's
work. We
[Music]
Shin, Shin, Shin. Oh,
Dad, oh, Dad. Look up. Dad is a
bit tired right now.
[Music]
Look, we can really do it today, right?
Oh,
not you. Today is a truly historic day.
If we succeed, Rio, because it's the
first time in your life you've succeeded. Rio, you have to carry it alone. Ah,
now you have the courage, right? Yes.
But this isn't it.
This is too heavy to carry. Take Dad's phone. You
know all the passwords, right? Oh, the passwords for coming in too. Ah, I know them all, so
now we can do it. If you forget the bad news, use
this walkie-talkie to find Dad and Mom. If the walkie-talkie does
n't work, use the phone. Oh, the walkie-talkie will work. But I don't know if we
can really make it.
Why am I suddenly trembling? Ah, I'm not trembling. If you're trembling, don't do it. I'm
not trembling. When we come in, the elevator is shaking. *Clap clap clap clap*. I think I'm trembling a little. Just a little.
No, right now, it's about 80%
excitement and 20% worry. Dad will be watching from here, up there. You can't be scared or afraid.
Suddenly... Dad has to stay calm. Got it?
Yes. But if I
mention the walkie-talkie, that's when Dad has to speak.
In the elevator, Dad immediately  If I tell
people, they might be surprised, you
know? Okay, I understand what you mean. It
might be embarrassing if Dad suddenly talks to you...
No, that's
not it. Okay. But what did you do and what did you do?
Ah, uh, chocolate popsicles.
Three chocolate popsicles. Riya, hurry up and eat some rice. You finished all the meat. Full. It's not that I'm full,
but right now I'm
losing my appetite because of the tension. Taste
[Music].
Look, just in case, just in case, don't follow those abstract people. You
know that well, right? Yeah, but let's
keep following them. Then, then, we have to call Dad.
Then Dad, hurry up and put on your clothes and come
down quickly. Oh no, where do you have
time to put on clothes? Dad, like this, run quickly.
Ah, run. Do you want to?
But if you succeed today, and as I
said before, you're overflowing with confidence and try to go alone
when Dad and Mom aren't around. You
can't do that anymore. Make sure, make sure you only go alone when
Dad and Mom are together.
Sometimes Mom, and sometimes Dad isn't around, but I only do it
when Dad is here. Just for now. Okay? Duck, you're
doing this just once. Yeah. Stay in one spot. Yeah, really,
really,
I'm really going. I'm not going to the car. No, I'm scared.
No, I'm going to go. I'm going to go. Yuya,
press the elevator button. Okay. You pressed the elevator button.
Pressed it. Yeah, there is something like that. I'm
trembling like this. You can do it. You're going now. Yeah, Lee,
fighting. Yeah, fighting. I'll
go. Dad's phone, B1, you know, right? Yeah. Just
a moment. Again, again.
Ryu, Ryu. Can you hear me well? Yeah, Dad.
Dad, I'll be watching from up here. It's okay. Yeah, Dad, I'll stay here. Mom... Yeah, you can
close the door. You can close it. Yeah. Okay.
Really, goodbye. Go ahead. Go ahead. Hurry up. Go ahead.
Dad will be watching from up there. Yeah. Yeah.
Heartless.
[Music]
Yeah.
Goodbye. Going down. The door
again. Oh my god. I don't know if I
can really go.
Dad. Dad.
Dad. Dad is here. It is a match.
The door becomes. Shoes. Shoes. Shoes. Shoes. Hey. Yeah.
Dad. Yeah.
Dad is watching from up there. Now. Trying to see Lee. Even a fishing boat is
hard.
If you did, ask your older sister. Don't tell me.
[Music]
Ma. It doesn't come up well.
Really. If you
look here. Ah, shall I open this for you? Yes.
Hmm, like this. Which one? Ah, I'm going to buy that. Yeah, I'll get it out for you.
Here.
[Music]
Thank you.
[Music] It is done. Success. Success. It is a success. Yeah, done.
Down. Running over. You're
really running. Ryu, don't run. Why are you running? Come
slowly. You can come slowly without running.
[Music]
Plus, please give me the work.
Rio
Hanida succeeded.
[Music]
Ola arrived. Since we arrived, [
Music] let's go. You
really teased me. Wow, wow.
Look at this. Three. Miya, why are you so good? Uh, uh, just pass by.
The uncle took it out for me. Wow, really, really. Uh, I should have said thank you.
I said thank you. Hey, I filmed all of this. I filmed everything.
I said thank you. Wow, now I guess I can greet
people well too. I should turn this off. Ah, you
really did well. Our Rio has grown so much.
Our Rio doesn't fit. Really. Meyer. Ah,
pay me
a lot.
[Music]
thought m